http://www.discovercard.com/privacy-statement/?ICMPGN=PUB_FTR_QL_PRIVACY

.
Remember User ID
Forgot User ID/Password?
Activate Credit Card
Register Your Account
Close
.
Privacy Center
Find out more about our privacy practices and how we work to keep your information protected
Online Policy
Link to Introduction pageIntroduction
Link to About the Information We Collect pageAbout the Information We Collect
Link to How We Use It pageHow We Use It
Link to What We Share pageWhat We Share
Link to Manage Your Privacy Choices pageManage Your Privacy Choices
Link to Home Loans pageHome Loans
Link to Identity Theft Protection pageIdentity Theft Protection
Link to Personal Loans pagePersonal Loans
Link to Student Loans pageStudent Loans
California Residents
Link to California Notice at Collection sectionCalifornia Notice at Collection
Link to California Consumer Privacy Act pageCalifornia Privacy Notice
Link to Make a Request pageMake a Request
European Union Data Subjects
Link to European Union Online Privacy Statement pageEuropean Union Online Privacy Statement
Contact Us About Privacy
For questions, or to learn more about Discover Financial Services' privacy statements and practices, here's how you can reach us:
Phone
1-800-DISCOVER
(1-800-347-2683)
Salt Lake City, UT 84130-0943
European Union data subjects with questions should follow the instructions Link to European Union Online Privacy Statement pagehere to contact Discover.
Resources
Link to SMS Terms & Conditions pageSMS Terms & Conditions
Link to Privacy Glossary pagePrivacy Glossary
Link to Terms of Use pageTerms of Use
Like Us on Facebook opens in a new window
Instagram opens in a new window
Contact with Us on LinkedIn opens in a new window
DISCOVER MOBILE APP
ACCREDITED BUSINESS opens in a new tab Opens in a new window
Member FDIC opens in a new tab Opens in a new window
©
Discover Bank, Member FDIC
